(Penny:)Um, waitress for six months
and then become a movie star.
Uh-huh.
(Leonard:)Was there a Plan B?
(Penny:)TV star.
Well, it's probably not as bad as you think.
Let's take a look.
(Leonard:)Maybe we can find some corners to cut.
(Leonard:)Oh, here's something.
(Leonard:)If you don't have electricity,
then you probably don't need cable.
(Leonard:)Just a suggestion.
A hundred and seventy dollars
for acting classes?
(Penny:)Oh, no, I can't give up my acting classes.
I'm a professional actress.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
You had an acting job
where you got paid?
[SCOFFS]
(Penny:)That is not the definition of professional.
Actually, it kind of is. Let's keep looking.
(Leonard:)Whoa.
What's $1800
to the Los Angeles County Superior Court?
(Penny:)Oh, that's nothing.
(Leonard:)Nothing?
(Leonard:)It sounds like you got caught speeding
going 4000 miles an hour.